今天我们请到了莉蒂夏·赖特
Today we have Letitia Wright.
-不可思议令人惊异的
- Amazing. -Amazing.
-我爱她 -她是最好的
-I love her. -Only the best.
神奇的工作
Amazing work.
美丽
Beautiful.
塔玛拉 劳伦斯
Tamara Lawrance.
哦,我的上帝 纳迪恩 马歇尔
Oh, my God. Nadine Marshall.
乔迪 梅
Jodhi May.
哦,我的上帝特维 艾蒂安
Oh, my God. Treva Etienne.
正确的
Right.
迈克尔 思迈里
Michael Smiley.
他总是让我微笑
He always makes me smile.
并介绍我们……
And introducing us...
伊娃·阿里安娜·巴克斯特和莉亚·蒙德斯·西蒙兹
Eva-Arianna Baxter and Leah Mondesir-Sionds.
很神奇的
amazing.
它们听起来太棒了
They just sound totally amazing.
他们是如此美妙
They're so wonderful.
我知道，我知道
I know, I know.
沉默的双胞胎
The Silent Twins.
测试，测试，一，二，一，二
Testing, testing, one, two, one, two.
欢迎
welcome
吉本斯电台，吉本斯，
to Radio Gibbons, Gibbons,
吉本斯
Gibbons.
吉本斯,吉本斯,
Gibbons, Gibbons,
吉本斯
Gibbons.
这是- 00点
It's- 00 p.m.
我们是你的主人，还有詹妮弗
We're your hosts, and Jennifer,
你加入我们是为了…
and you're joining us for...
《生活的现实》
The Living Facts of Life.
今天我们将讨论如何处理离婚
Today we'll be discussing how to handle a divorce.
是的，分离是非常艰难的
Yes, separations are very tough.
这很难，但在你昂首挺胸的情况下是可能做到的
Difficult, but possible to do while keeping your head high.
即使你嫁给了天蝎座
Even if you've married a Scorpio.
不，不，别这么做
No, no, don't do that.
下次，考虑一下天秤座
Next time, consider a Libra.
他们是有礼貌和体贴的人
They're polite and considerate people.
人类的苦难
The suffering of men.
男人被我们迷住了，认为女人是他们的上级
Men are dazzled by us and think women are their superiors.
他们陷入了痛苦的伤痛之中
They get caught up in a painful web of hurt
充满了愤怒和绝望
filled with anger and desperation.
也许这能帮你记起来
Perhaps it will help you to remember
男人讨厌女人，但却离不开女人
that men hate women but cannot live without them.
爱一个人是有可能的
It's possible to love someone so much
你受不了她
you can't stand her
同时，又想让她死
and, at the same time, to want her dead.
我想爱也可能是毁灭
I suppose love can also be destruction.
受的让我们休息一下
-Moving on. Let's take a break.
雷克斯霸王龙的《热恋》
With "Hot Love" by T. Rex.
这个晴朗的星期一下午来找你
Coming at you this fine Monday afternoon.
晚餐时间
Dinnertime.
你输了
You lost.
不,我没有
No, I didn't.
是的,你做到了
Yes, you did.
-不,我没有是的,你做到了
-No, I didn't. -Yes, you did.
你感动
You moved.
我赢了
I win.
你输了
You lose.
骗子
Liar.
我没有动
I did not move.
你输了
You lost.
…的竞争
...competition.
细节是弗利特伍德麦克
The, uh, details were Fleetwood Mac
来自Fleetwood Mac专辑中的《I'm So Afraid》
from the album Fleetwood Mac with "I'm So Afraid."
有请t恤冠军，杰夫·沃勒…
Let's call in our T-shirt winner, uh, Geoff Waller...
你永远找不到快乐
You'll never find joy
如果你想一个人呆着
if you want to be alone.
你永远也找不到快乐
You will never find joy
如果你想一个人呆着
if you want to be alone.
我到家了每个人都好吗?
I'm home. Everybody all right?
-奥布里，随便吃吧
- Aubrey, so, help yourself to dinner.
我改变罗西
I'm changing Rosie.
姑娘们，今天过得怎么样?嗯?
How was your day, girls? Huh?
-在学校吗?的节日葛丽塔
-How was school? -David. Greta.
-好吗?头里
-Good? -Come down here.
好吧，来了
Yeah, all right, coming.
我们今天会吃顿好晚餐的，是吧?
We'll have a nice dinner today, huh?
好了，我们去拿盘子
Right, let's get the plates.
所有的食物，好吗，姑娘们?
All of your food, okay, girls?
大卫，你能去接电话吗?
David, you want to get the phone?
-亲爱的，来点豌豆吗?是吗?
- Sweetheart, you want some peas? Yes?
-你想吃豌豆吗，亲爱的?-你好吗?
-You want some peas, eh, darling? -Hello?
-格里塔，你想吃豌豆吗?-不,谢谢
-Greta, do you want some peas? -No, thank you.
妈妈今天给你吃豌豆好的
- Muy feed you some peas today. Okay.
姑娘们，你们今天有作业吗?
You got homework today, girls?
没有?
No?
我没有听到回答
I didn't hear an answer.
葛丽塔,来吧
Greta, come on.
他们得把脑袋打在一起
They need to get their heads bashed together.
1乘以6等于6
One times six is six.
2乘以6等于12
Two times six is 12.
3乘以6等于18
Three times six is 18.
4乘以6等于24
Four times six is 24.
-你傻吗?未来过
-You stupid or what? -Boo.
往下咽
Swallow it.
医生-我们结束了，凯瑟琳·詹金斯
DR.- We're done, Catherine Jenkins.
在运行
Run along.
接下来,请
Next up, please.
你能对我保持冷静吗?
Do you think you could keep a stiff upper lip for me?
只有一个
Just one.
你很害怕吗?
Are you very scared?
你呢?
What about you?
你害怕吗?
Are you scared?
里斯博士认为，这个问题超出了学校的帮助范围
Dr. Rees feels this issue goes beyond the school's help.
请理解，我有1500名学生
Please understand, I have 1,500 students.
我正忙着对付那些麻烦的人
My hands are full dealing with the ones who are trouble.
对于那些不交流的人，我无能为力
I can't do much about the ones who don't counicate.
我们什么都没对孩子们做
We didn't do nothing to the babies.
他们是完美的
-They were perfect.
他们咯咯直笑
They giggled.
他们对我说，
They spoke to me,
然后就越来越少了
and then it was just less and less, you know.
但是什么都没有发生
But nothing happened.
坏什么都没有发生
Nothing bad happened.
你是巴巴多斯人?
You're originally from Barbados?
是的嗯…皇家空军把我们搬到了英国
Yes. Um... the RAF moved us to Britain.
我是空中交通管制员
I am an air traffic controller.
哦
Oh.
我们被告知,
We were told,
让他们去普通学校，戴维斯先生
keep them in a normal school, Mr. Davis.
青春期会解决这个问题
Adolescence will resolve this.
他们需要良好的教育
They need a good education.
他们需要去上学
They need to be in school.
他们总是在卧室里聊天
They speak all the time in the bedroom.
你知道，他们只是害羞
They're just shy, you know.
吉本斯夫人,请
Mrs. Gibbons, please.
他们进不了像样的学校
They won't get on in a proper school
如果他们不会说英语
if they don't speak English.
我们将让女孩们接受特殊教育
We will move the girls into special education.
我们会让他们开口的
We'll get them to talk yet.
过来
Come along.
女孩,加油
Girls, come on.
这是一个全新的开始
It's a fresh start.
你好,朱恩你好,珍妮佛
Hello, June. Hello, Jennifer.
我叫蒂姆·托马斯
My name is Tim Thomas.
我是你的老师
I'm your teacher.
好的
Okay.
我在这里录了一些问题，
I've recorded some questions here,
我已经留了足够的空间给你回答了
and I've left enough space for you to answer.
但如果你不想回答我的问题
But if you don't want to answer my questions
或者你觉得我的问题不太好，
or you don't think my questions are very good,
非常非常欢迎你对我大喊大叫
you're very, very welcome to shout at me,
“托马斯先生，你的问题都是垃圾”
"Mr. Thomas, your questions are rubbish."
好吗?
Okay?
我把门关上
I'll close the door.
提姆:你觉得你的新学校怎么样?
TIM What do you think of your new school?
你有什么爱好吗?
Do you have any hobbies?
你喜欢猫吗?
Do you like cats?
你喜欢听什么样的音乐?
What kind of music do you listen to?
你业余时间喜欢做什么?
What do you like doing during your free time?
你如何描述自己的性格?
How would you describe your personalities?
蒂姆:你最喜欢的科目是什么?
TIM What is your favorite subject?
你更喜欢哪一个，阳光还是雨?
Which do you like better, sunshine or rain?
詹妮弗，琼，你们养过宠物吗?
Jennifer, June, have you ever had a pet?
两只非常快乐的小鹦鹉
Two little parrots who were very jolly.
然后珀金斯死了，可怜的波莉哭了
Then Perkins died, and poor Polly cried.
可怜的珀金斯和波莉
Poor little Perkins and Polly.
两只非常快乐的小鹦鹉
Two little parrots who were very jolly.
然后珀金斯死了，可怜的波莉哭了
Then Perkins died, and poor Polly cried.
可怜的珀金斯和波莉
Poor little Perkins and Polly.
从前，有两只鹦鹉
Once, there were two parrots
他们在动物园里长大
who were brought up to live in a zoo.
每天，人们都会来动物园
Every day, people would come to the zoo
-看鹦鹉
-and see the parrots.
-有时鹦鹉
-Sometimes the parrots
会嘲笑说话的人，
would mock the talking people,
有时候他们会
and sometimes they would actually
进行他们之间的对话
have a conversation between themselves.
人们会站在那里
The people would stand there
几乎所有的一天
-nearly all day
-听鹦鹉的对话-
-listening to the parrots' conversation.  -
-人们认为这有点奇怪-
-The people thought it was a bit weird  -
两只鹦鹉能像人类一样说话
for two parrots to talk as well as humans did.
鹦鹉的名字是波莉和珀金斯，
The parrots, whose names were Polly and Perkins,
经常谈论他们是多么渴望
often talked of how they longed
回到他们的祖国
to get back to their native land.
有时他们会问守望者
Sometimes they would ask the watchers
打开笼子的门，放他们出去
to open the cage doors and let them out.
人们经常会笑
The people would often laugh
-并且认为鹦鹉是在开玩笑
- -and think the parrots were kidding.
一些正在观看的孩子
Some of the children who were watching
问他们的父母
asked their parents
如果他们能把鹦鹉带回家
if they could take the parrots home with them.
有时，父母还没来得及回答，
Sometimes, before the parents had time to answer,
一只鹦鹉会好心地说……
one parrot would kindly say...
-“我们不卖我们是非卖品”
- "We're not for sale. We're not for sale."
另一只鹦鹉也会说同样的话
And the other parrot would say the same.
-“我们不卖我们是非卖品”
- "We're not for sale. We're not for sale."
“我是一个非常非常大的人，我来接你”
"I am a very, very big man, and I'm coming to get you."
“不,你不是
"No, you're not.
你不能带我们去任何地方”
You're not taking us anywhere."
“是的,我是”
"Yes, I am."
“不,你不是走开，走开，走开”
"No, you're not. Go away, go away, go away."
“味道会非常非常非常好”
"It'll taste very, very, very good."
“不，你不能吃我们
"No, you're not gonna eat us.
我们不是好吃”
We're not tasty."
-“我带你去”
- "I will take you."
-“没有走开，走开
-"No. Go away, go away.
“不要把我们别把我们带走
"Don't take us. Don't take us away.
不，不，不没有”
No, no, no, no. No."
“我想花300英镑买他们的肝脏，
"I want to have their liver for 300 pounds,
"那么你的心脏就只值一英镑，
"and then your heart will only be one pound,
“我就把它吃了
"and I'll eat it.
它会很美味，很温暖”
And it will be nice, tasty and warm."
我动，你跟着
I move, you follow.
我跟着，你动
I follow, you move.
你动，我动
You move, I move.
-我跟着，你走
-I follow, you move.
姑娘们，你们做得很好
Girls, you're doing beautifully.
你，我，我们，我
You, me, we, I.
跟我来，不然你就死定了
Follow me else you die.
头里-哦,珍妮
-Come on. -Oh, Jenny.
詹妮弗，你为什么这么做?
Jennifer, why did you do that?
你对吧?你都好吗?
-You all right? -Are you okay?
詹妮弗，你为什么这么做?
Jennifer, why did you do that?
听着，我就直说吧
Look, I'll get straight to the point.
如果你有什么想跟我说的，
If there's something you want to counicate to me,
你最好现在就说
you best say it now.
你看,我……
You see, I...
我觉得你们可能会对彼此产生不好的影响
I think you might be a bad influence on each other.
也许……是个好主意
It might be an idea to...
把你们分开一段时间
split you up for a while.
你们可以去弗洛伊德医生的公寓，
One of you can go to Dr. Floyd's residential unit,
离这里不远
which isn't far from here,
那另一个可以留在这里
then the other one can stay here.
你怎么看?
What do you think?
你要说什么吗?
Are you going to say anything?
好的我,嗯…
Okay. I, uh...
我要离开房间了……
I'll leave the room...
让你们俩决定谁去哪
and let both of you work out who goes where.
好吧?
All right?
我就在外面
I'll just be out here.
我给他们几分钟时间
I'm giving them a few minutes.
我讨厌你!
I hate you!
哦,我的上帝
Oh, my God.
-你什么都不是!你是珍妮佛!
- You are nobody! You are Jennifer!
-你是我!-女孩女孩,停止
-You are me! -Girls. Girls, stop.
-你很快就会回来的，琼
- You'll be home again before you know it, June.
永远在一起
Together forever and ever.
永远默默地在一起
Together forever in silence.
你和我
You and me.
我和你
Me and you.
来吧,朱恩
Come on, June.
为你而做
Do it for you.
为我们做吧
Do it for we.
为我做吧
Do it for me.
为我们做吧
Do it for us.
拜托
Please.
珍妮弗!
-Jennifer!
詹妮弗,停止!詹妮弗,停止!
-Jennifer, stop! -Jennifer, stop!
-嘿,嘿
-Hey, hey.
嘿，快过来
Hey, come here now.
-嘿,冷静下来
-Hey, calm down.
头里
-Come back.
我带回家
I've brought home.
好的
Okay.
圣诞快乐,小狗
Merry Christmas, puppy.
每个人的未来
Everyone's coming over.
我想和他们坐在一起
I want us to sit with them.
和他们吃
Eat with them.
你怎么看?
What do you think?
我们必须选择合适的时机
We have to choose the right moment.
-格洛丽亚，那个看起来不错-好的
-Gloria, that one look great, man. -Okay.
-嘿，格里塔，去把…-大卫，拿果汁来
-Hey, Greta, go and put the... -David, bring the juice.
马克，你把礼物放在那边
Mark, you put the presents over there.
来自那里让我们看看孩子，伙计
Come through there. Let's see the baby, man.
-让我们看看孩子-哦…
-Let's see the baby. -Oh...
看看她，嗯?看看她
Ah, look at her, huh? Just look at her.
-这就是我所做的-过来，看看这个婴儿
-It's all I do. -Come here, look at the baby.
-我无法停止凝视-来看看我们家，伙计
-I can't stop staring. -Come and see the family, man.
美丽,是吗?看看这个
Beautiful, huh? Look at that.
这一个
This one.
我应该把礼物放在树下还是桌子上?
Should I put the presents under the tree or on the table?
在桌子上-好的
-On the table. -Okay.
和…
And...
…孩子可能是素食主义者，但我给她做了火鸡
...the baby might be vegetarian, but I made her a turkey.
是,好吗?
Is that okay?
是的
Yeah.
-还有，还有家庭
- And, and then there's the family.
所以…有一个木乃伊……
So... there's a muy...
…爸爸,露西,苏西
...daddy, Lucy, Suzie
和《末路狂花》疯狂
and Thelma crazy.
所以我们走进客厅说…
So we walk into the living room and we say...
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
说得有点慢，但我会跟上你的
Said it a bit slow, but I'll keep up with you.
好吧，快一点
Okay, a bit faster, then.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
你为什么不上楼给双胞胎们看看孩子?
Why don't you pop upstairs and show the twinnies the baby?
我知道他们很乐意收留她
I know they'd love to hold her.
他们一整天都在干什么
What have they been doing all day
现在学校跟他们绝交了?
now that school's done with them?
-哦,音乐-
-Oh, music. -
阅读
Reading.
你知道的
You know.
所以,相同的
So, the same.
不不
No. No.
带她
Take her up.
事实上，我想他们给她做了一些玩偶
In fact, I think they made her some dolls.
大卫，我少了一个叉子
David, I'm missing a fork.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
把盘子拿来
And bring the plates.
-好的-好的，我把他们带进来
-The good ones. -Okay, I'll bring them in.
我给你带来了海伦·玛丽
I've brought you Helen Marie.
克里斯快乐……
Merry Chris...
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
我给你带来了海伦·玛丽
I've brought you Helen Marie.
你愿意的话可以抱着她
You can hold her if you like.
妈妈说你给她做了礼物
Muy said you made her a gift.
朱恩?
June?
詹妮弗，你手里拿的是什么?
Jennifer, what's in your hand?
是给海伦·玛丽的吗?
Is it for Helen Marie?
它很好
It's nice.
我尝试
I'm trying.
你至少可以说点什么吧
You could at least say something.
真的吗?
Really?
你一直都是我的负担
You've been a burden on me all my life.
这是家庭的耻辱
An embarrassment to the family.
你可以烂在这里
You can rot in here.
在你肮脏的小房间里，
In your filthy little room,
拿着你那堆皱巴巴的纸
with your piles of crumpled paper
还有你吃了一半的食物
and your bits of half-eaten food.
这是我最后一次努力了
This is the last time I make an effort.
我完成了
I'm done.
马克,我们离开
Mark, we're leaving.
我们要离开发生了什么?
-We're leaving. -What happened?
-双胞胎说什么了吗?我们要离开
-Did the twinnies say something? -We're leaving.
是的,妈妈
Yeah, Mum.
他们说:“圣诞快乐
They said, "Merry Christmas.
世界和平我们非常爱你”
Peace on Earth. We love you so much."
不…
No...
哦,主耶稣
Oh, Lord Jesus.
别哭了没关系
Don't cry. It's all right.
没关系没关系
It's all right. It's okay.
-圣诞节后，乌云笼罩
-After Christmas, black clouds hang over
帕伦博家族
the Pallenberg family.
哔哔的声音镜头转Delroy Pallenberg
-Beep. -John Delroy Pallenberg
是一名外科医生，他的妻子米歇尔·德尔罗伊·帕伦伯格
is a surgeon whose wife, Michelle Delroy Pallenberg,
已经因为先天性心脏缺陷失去了两个孩子
has already lost two babies from a congenital heart defect.
不幸的是，他们最新的孩子，韦恩·肖恩，
Unfortunately, their latest child, Wayne Shane,
被诊断出患有同样的心脏病
is diagnosed as having the same heart condition
只剩下两周的生命了
and given only two weeks to live.
帕伦伯格博士决定采取英勇的措施
Dr. Pallenberg decides on heroic measures
为了救他的孩子
to save his child.
“米歇尔，我们都希望孩子能活下来，不是吗?”
"Michelle, we both want the baby to live, don't we?"
米歇尔点了点头
Michelle nodded her head.
-“是的，约翰，我们知道”
-"Yes, John, we do."
所以鲍比要为我们做这件事
"And so Bobby is going to do it for us
因为如果没有这种可能性
"because without that possibility
我们的儿子快要死了”
our son is going to die."
米歇尔低头盯着鲍比看了一会儿，
Michelle for a while gazed down at Bobby,
他那双棕色的大眼睛似乎奇怪地关心着
his large brown eyes seeming strangely concerned
仿佛他已经敏锐地觉察到了什么
-as though he had perceived something shrewdly,  -
奇怪的是
curiously.
房间里笼罩着一种深沉的寂静，
The room took on the presence of a heavy hush,
伴随着暗影的窃窃私语一个日益增长的秘密
accompanied by the shadowed whispers of a growing secret.
写学校
The Writing School.
“创意写作函授课程
"A correspondence course in creative writing
不仅能提高你的写作风格
"will not only improve your writing style
而是帮助你推销你的故事”
but help you sell your stories."
珍妮
Jenny.
等待,等待等一下，等一下，等一下
Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
上面写着89英镑的报名费
- It says 89 pounds enrollment fee.
那我们怎么负担得起呢?
Well, how are we gonna afford that?
上面写着，为了有资格上这门课，
Says, "In order to qualify for the course,
什么是不该写的
"what not to write about.
“编辑这个阶层不喜欢酒鬼，
"Editors as a class dislikes drunkards,
“疯子,吸毒者,
"lunatics, drug addicts,
“妓女和作者,
"prostitutes and authors,
“残疾或畸形的关键人物，
"crippled or deformed key characters,
“不愉快的孩子,
"unpleasant children,
“吸烟和喝酒的青少年
"adolescents who smoke and drink.
“其他编辑不喜欢的是精神家园，
"Other editorial dislikes are mental homes,
严重或不治之症
"serious or incurable diseases.
葬礼也是禁忌”
Funerals are also a taboo."
我们可以这么做
We could do that.
-社会保险号码、姓名和地址
- Social Security number, name and address.
这是你的好处
And here's your benefit.
看
Look.
老朱莉的外面,
Old Julie's outside,
又在监视我们
spying on us again.
是啊，我能看到你看到我
Yeah, I can see you see me.
一直走
Keep walking.
你一生的挚爱来了，珍妮邮递员
Love of your life is here, Jenny. Postman.
他有包裹吗?
Has he got a package?
珍妮,你看-它到达吗?
-Jenny, look. -Did it arrive?
是的
Yeah.
谈话的艺术
The Art of Conversation.
打开它，打开它
Open it, open it.
-你怎么打开它?-恩……
-How do you open it? -Um...
推动和提升
Push and lift.
我们现在的作家
We're writers now.
我们现在的作家-是的
-We're writers now. -Yes.
上面说他们接受我们的申请
It says they accept our application
有33%的折扣
with a 33% discount
我们都是8201学生
and we are both student 8201.
我们的第一个作业要在四周后交
Our first assignment is due in four weeks' time.
需要更多墨水
Gonna need more ink.
我今天会发生什么事?
What can be happening to me today?
我觉得自己好像在游泳池里游泳;
I feel as though I'm swiing in a pool;
海水冲刷着我的脚，
by the sea washing up to touch my feet,
我尝到了盐的甜香;
I taste the sweet smell of salt;
咸水在我的脚趾间流过，
salt water running in between my toes,
咸咸的水从我的眼睛里流出，
salt water running from my eyes,
抚摸我冰冷的纸手……
to touch my cold and papery hands...
我身上会发生什么事?
What can be happening to me;
我可以伸手触摸星星;
I can reach out and touch the stars;
我能看到木星，金星;
I can see Jupiter, Venus;
我能看到银河系
I can see the galaxy
然后我发现了地球
And then I spot the earth
看到一个缺失的空间;
and see a missing space;
我缺少空间
my missing space.
他们都拒绝
They're all rejections.
他们所有人
All of them.
丰塔纳第二次拒绝我
My second rejection from Fontana.
BBC说他们不会读你的剧本
And the BBC says they won't read your play
因为他们不了解你
because they don't know you.
他们当然不想听我们的故事，珍妮
Course they don't want our stories, Jenny.
为了写出一本好书，你需要去感受它
In order to write a good book, you need to feel it.
你必须受到鼓舞
You have to be inspired.
或者有更多的感觉
Or feel something more than this.
需要爱
Need love.
需要浪漫
Need romance.
是这个吗?我是这样认为的
-Is this it? -I think so.
如此多的乳房
So many breasts.
朱恩看
June. Look.
他留着我们的香烟
He kept our cigarettes.
看
Look.
哦，他太浪漫了
Oh, he's so romantic.
我的美国的爱人
My American lover.
珍妮
Jenny.
-他们肯定在约会
- They're definitely, definitely dating.
-是吗?-是的，她告诉我的
-Yeah? -Yes, she told me.
她告诉我…
-She told me...
停!
Stop!
-你们两个从哪里来，基地吗?
- Where do you two come from, the base?
他们很害怕，乔治
They are scared, George.
你来看过我的一个儿子吗?
Did you come around to see one of my boys?
我的孩子们都是真正的捣乱分子
My boys are genuine hell-raisers.
你知道的，对吧?
You know that, right?
韦恩!去你妈的，你个大混蛋
Wayne! Fuck you, you massive shit.
去舔鸡巴吧，混蛋
Go suck a cock, asshole.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
他们把你赶出学校了吗?
Did they kick you out of school, huh?
你嗨过吗?
You, uh, ever get high?
嘿，把那玩意给我
Hey, give that shit to me.
把它那就这样吧
Take it. There you go.
准备好了,詹妮弗?
Ready, Jennifer?
到这里来不要害怕
Come here. Don't be scared.
它在呼吸
Breathe it in.
就是这样
That's it.
也许能让你放松一点
Might loosen you up a bit.
是的,是的
Yeah, yeah.
就是这样
That's it.
朱恩
June.
你也一样
You do the same.
-就是这样
-That's it.
呼吸
-Breathe it in.
就是这样
That's it.
你们两个真是疯婆子
You two are some crazy goddamn bitches.
大的呼吸
Big breath, right.
-对吗?
-All right?
我想她喜欢
I think she likes it.
出生于- 00，
was born at- 00,
我出生于- 10
and I was born at- 10.
所以我有一个很好的，强大的，
Which is why I have a good, strong,
一个善良、坚强的白羊座
a good, strong Aries in me.
下内存
Under the Ram.
她有时也很不可预测
She can also be really unpredictable,
就像白羊座一样
just like an Aries.
真不敢相信你会说话
I can't believe you can talk.
-嗯,我们可以
-Well, we can.
我们可以做很多事情
There's a lot of things we can do.
我是天秤座
-I'm a Libra.
当然
Of course.
-他当然是天秤座的当然
-Of course he's a Libra. -Of course.
跟我说说我
Tell me about me.
星星怎么说?
What do the stars say?
他们说我的鸡鸡很大吗?
Do they say that I have a huge cock?
不
No.
-公寓里充满了寂寞的气氛
-The apartment was filled with the lonesome atmosphere
沉睡的墓地
of a sleeping cemetery.
-的嗡嗡声
-The buzzing sound
从冰箱里出来的声音变成了深深的叹息
coming from the refrigerator turned to a deep sigh
普雷斯顿打开盒子，拿出一罐百事可乐
as Preston opened it to yank out a Pepsi-Cola can.
电话开始响了起来
The phone began to peal.
普雷斯顿停了下来他的心跑
Preston stopped. His heart raced.
他焦急地想着佩吉
And anxiously, he thought about Peggy.
她远在千里之外
She was a million miles away.
喂?
Hello?
普雷斯顿，是你吗?
Preston, is that you?
佩吉的声音攻击了他的耳朵
Peggy's voice attacked his ears.
我们不会离开马里布的
We're not leaving Malibu.
你在听吗?
Are you listening?
我爱你，我不能去旧金山
I love you, and I can't go to San Francisco.
我得告诉你件事，普雷斯顿
I've gotta tell you something, Preston.
我们不会离开马里布的
We're not leaving Malibu.
你在听吗?
Are you listening?
我爱你，我不能去旧金山
I love you, and I can't go to San Francisco.
疼痛震聋了他的耳膜
The pain deafened his eardrums.
他瘫倒在地板上
He sank to the floor...
电话摔在他身边
...the phone crashing down beside him.
他是下降,
-He was falling,
漂浮在空荡荡的黑色隧道里，
floating in an empty black tunnel,
就像被困在太空中的火箭
like a rocket trapped in space.
-一罐百事可乐
-A can of Pepsi-Cola
扭扭捏捏地向他走来
came twisting and turning towards him.
它坠毁
It crashed.
就因为你突然灵光一现，
Just because you've had a burst of inspiration,
并不意味着你的书会比我的好
doesn't mean your book's going to be better than mine.
你只是嫉妒我的专注
You're just jealous of my focus.
你是一个黑客
You're a hack.
昨晚的梦……
Last night's dream...
是的!
Yes!
珍妮，新视野说他们会出版我的书
Jenny, New Horizon said they'll publish my book
一个月80英镑
for 80 pounds a month.
我需要你的一点救济金
I'm gonna need a little bit of your dole.
我需要那笔钱写书
Well, I need that money for my book
因为这将是一场绝杀
because it's going to be a knockout.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你写了一堆垃圾
You're writing a bunch of crap,
反正也没人接受
and no one's accepting it anyway.
别那么粗鲁!
Don't be rude!
听着，这对我来说很重要
Look, this is a big deal for me.
阅读它看
Read it. Look.
我能得到什么好处?
And what do I get out of it?
当你的书被接受的时候，
Well, when you actually get your book accepted,
我会把钱都给你的，我发誓
I'll give you all my money, I swear.
拜托
Please.
是的!
Yes!
好的第一件事,
Okay. First things,
我们需要拍专业的照片
we need to take professional photos.
好吧?来吧微笑
All right? Come on. Smile.
我们去楼下吧
Let's go downstairs.
完美的好的
Perfect. Okay.
确保你的脸是这样的
Make sure your face is like this.
-边吗?是的,看起来专业
-To the side? -Yes, looking professional.
-好的,但是……华丽的
-Okay, but... -Gorgeous.
是的，但要有一个正确的角度
Yeah, but get that right angle
因为我不想看起来很胖
because I don't want to look fat.
我的脸看起来胖吗?
Does my face look fat?
风格的伟大-嗯
-Looking great. -h.
微笑
Smile.
好的
Okay.
不不
No. No.
哦,上帝,不
Oh, God, no.
-不,不,不可怕的,不-我不喜欢这些
-No, no, no. Terrible, no. -I don't like these.
我在那里做什么?-看这头发
-What am I doing there? -Look at this hair.
那是什么?
What is that?
那是什么?你为什么让我这么做?
What is that? Why did you tell me to do that?
-这张照片的构图不…-哦,我的上帝
-The composition of this photo does not... -Oh, my God.
我应该更认真地对待我的饮食
I should have been so much more serious about that diet.
-我长斑了看那个斑点在那里
- I've got spots. Look at that spot. There.
-哦,不我太胖了，找不到出版商
- Oh, no. I'm way too fat to find a publisher.
最后是Michael Hyams，
YOUNG And finally Michael Hyams,
在埃塞克斯达格南乌节路11号
from 11 Orchard Road, Dagenham in Essex.
祝贺你,帮派
Congratulations, gang.
我得说，音乐爱好者们，
And, uh, I must say, music lovers,
我认为我们选择了他有史以来最伟大的表演，
I think we've chosen his greatest performance ever,
鲍勃·迪伦，选自《欲望》专辑，
Bob Dylan there, taken from the album Desire,
一个叫…
the one called...
拿着
Take it.
你呆在那儿，朱尼·朱恩
You stay there, Juney June.
你不移动
Don't you move.
-这是我甜蜜人生中最美好的日子之一
-One of the best days of my sweet life.
我婚前有过性行为
I had sex before marriage.
到处都是血
There was lots of blood.
对不起,上帝
Sorry, God.
你的朋友,珍妮
Your friend, Jenny.
是的
Yeah.
喔!喔!
Whoo. Whoo.
哦，你真幸运
Oh, you lucky girl.
今晚轮到你了，Juney June
It's your turn tonight, Juney June.
是的
Yeah.
我知道你还在我的魔法中
I know I still have you under my spell.
你这样认为吗?
You think so?
是啊，你更像我
Yeah, you're more like me.
那是因为我们的灵魂是火热的和好胜的
That's 'cause our souls are fiery and competitive.
我们都有神秘的风格
We both have mysterious styles.
我们可以一起犯罪，韦恩
We can be partners in crime, Wayne.
你要和我一起抢劫吗?
Ah, are you gonna rob with me?
-是的-是吗?
-Yes. -Yeah?
-和我一起抢人?
-Mug people with me?
-是吗?
-Yeah?
你抽烟的样子很滑稽
You look funny when you smoke.
你想和我一起纵火吗?
You want to set fires with me?
-是吗?当然
-Yeah? -Of course.
哦,是的
Oh, yeah.
-什么?不,韦恩,不…
-What? No, Wayne, don't...
什么是错的?怎么了?不要这样做
-What's wrong? What's wrong? -Don't do that.
给它回来你准备好了吗?
-Give it back. -You ready?
停下来，不，不，不要!
-Stop. No, no, no, don't!
不，不，
No, no, no, no, no, no!
喔!琼，你看到了吗?
Whoo. June, you seeing this?
朱恩!
June!
别那样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
离开我!
Get off me!
对不起
Sorry.
你为什么这么做?
Why did you do that?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我爱你
-I love you.
我很抱歉我很抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉我爱你
I'm sorry. I love you.
我非常爱你我很抱歉我很抱歉
I love you so much. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我爱你我很抱歉
I love you. I'm so sorry.
别让他那样对你
Don't let him treat you like that.
他们沿着通道走回去
They make their way back down the aisle
热烈的欢迎等待着他们
to the tumultuous welcome awaiting them
在圣保罗大教堂的台阶上
at the steps of St Paul's.
就这样，在阳光下，在钟声中，在疯狂的喜悦中
And so, out into sunshine and bells and wild delight
作为一种明显的爱和骄傲的浪潮
as a palpable wave of affection and pride
威尔斯从人群中脱颖而出
wells out from the crowd.
从我们的生活中消失
Gone from our lives
就像潮水从海岸涌来
like the tides from the shore.
我对性没有感觉
I've got no feeling for sex,
但我无法忍受没有浪漫的生活
but I can't bear life without romance.
-我们不能回到空虚的日子
-We can't go back to the empty days
在我们找到爱之前
before we found love.
你偷的是火柴吗?
Were it matchsticks you stole?
喂?
Hello?
警察、救护车还是消防队?
Police, ambulance or fire?
-我打电话来是因为我们要坦白一件事
- I'm calling 'cause we've got a confession to make.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
我们要把整个哈弗威斯特都烧了
We're gonna burn the whole of Haverfordwest down.
我们不介意进监狱
We don't mind going to prison.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
什么?
What?
他想知道我们的名字
He wants to know our names.
名字是韦恩和卡尔，这是我们的名字
Names are Wayne and Carl, that's our names.
韦恩和卡尔韦恩……
Wayne and Carl. Wayne...
想知道我们住在哪里吗?
Want to know where we live as well?
想知道我们的地址吗?
Want to know our fucking address?
这是我们该死的地址!
Here's our fucking address!
来,来,来
Come, come, come.
跟我来
Follow me.
这种方式
This way.
在这里
There it is.
看汽车
-Watch the car.
去你妈的,混蛋!
Fuck you, asshole!
珍妮珍妮
Jenny. Jenny.
珍妮
Jenny.
是警察、救护车还是消防队?
WOPolice, ambulance or fire?
警察,请
Police, please.
我要坦白一件事
I have a confession to make.
我们烧毁了一家拖拉机店
We burnt down a tractor store...
-…在夏福韦斯
-...in Haverfordwest.
是的，我们现在到了
Yeah, we're here now.
如果可以的话抓住我们
Catch us if you can.
洛林吉本斯
Lorraine Gibbons,
你被指控犯有以下罪名
you are charged with the following counts.
你和另一个人，
You did jointly, with another,
进入某栋建筑，作为非法侵入者，
enter a certain building, as a trespasser,
偷25支铅笔，一副耳机，
steal 25 pencils, one pair of headphones,
一个电钟，一把剪刀，
an electric clock, a pair of scissors,
和一盒培乐多
and a carton of Play-Doh,
总价值为40英镑50便士
of a value together of 40 pounds and 50 pence.
1981年10月15日到18日之间，
Between the 15th and 18th of October 1981,
在戴菲德郡的哈弗福德韦斯特
at Haverfordwest in the county of Dyfed,
以非法闯入者的身份进入了某栋建筑，
did enter a certain building, as a trespasser,
偷里面的饮料和食物
steal therein drink and food items
价值5英镑24便士
to the value of five pounds and 24 pence.
1981年10月20日，
And on the 20th day of October 1981,
无正当理由，烧毁拖拉机店
without lawful excuse, damaged by fire a tractor store.
洛林吉本斯
Lorraine Gibbons,
你如何辩护，有罪还是无罪?
how do you plead, guilty or not guilty?
还有你，艾莉森·吉本斯
And you, Alison Gibbons,
都以同样的罪名被起诉
have been charged on the same counts.
你如何辩护，有罪还是无罪?
How do you plead, guilty or not guilty?
汉密尔顿医生，谢谢你出席今天的庭审
Uh, Dr. Hamilton, uh, thank you for attending court today.
你能告诉法庭你的意见吗
Could you please tell the court your opinion
你是如何发现每个被告的心理状态的
on how you found each of the defendants' state of mind
当你检查他们的时候?
when you examined them?
你能不能给法庭
And could you give the court
你有什么建议吗?
your recoendations that you have?
我的专业意见是每个被告
My professional opinion is that each defendant
患有精神疾病
suffers from a mental illness.
一种精神错乱，一种如此程度的亚正常状态
A psychopathic disorder, a subnormality of such a degree
把他们关在医院里
to warrant their detention in a hospital
接受治疗
for medical treatment.
因此，入学已经安排好了
As such, admission has been arranged
布罗德莫精神病院的医院
for Broadmoor Hospital.
Broadmoor有设施吗
Does Broadmoor have facilities
他们这个年龄的人需要的?
that people of their age require?
对这么年轻的人来说，这并不常见
It is not, not usual for persons so young
来布罗德莫监狱
to come to Broadmoor.
不过，我觉得和还押中心相比，
Uh, however, I think compared to the remand centre,
布罗德莫尔精神病院提供了一定的自由和治疗
Broadmoor offers a certain freedom and also therapy.
他们在那里的治疗
Uh, their treatment there
包括教他们说话
will consist of teaching them to speak.
我们保持着一种村庄般的氛围
And we maintain a sort of village-like atmosphere
在医院
at the hospital.
有花园
There are gardens.
我们有，理发师，
Uh, we have, uh, hairdressers,
漂亮的浴室等等
uh, beautiful bathrooms, and such.
维持病人健康的运动设施
Sports facilities for maintaining patients' fitness.
对了，我们还有个游泳池
Oh, and, uh, we even have a swiing pool.
-如果这是你的建议，汉密尔顿医生
- If that is your recoendation, Dr. Hamilton,
那么根据我们掌握的信息
then regarding the information we have as to
他们倾向于对自己造成危险
their tendencies to be dangerous to themselves
互相问候，
and to each other mutually,
鉴于预后的困难，
and in view of the difficulty of the prognosis,
你能推荐我下这个订单吗
would you recoend that the order I make
是否不受时间限制?
shall be without limit of time?
是的
Yes.
-他们判双胞胎无期徒刑?
- They giving the twinnies a life sentence?
好的
Okay.
好吧，我想出来了
Okay, I figured it out.
朱恩
June.
琼，来吧，这是我们的机会
June, come on, this is our chance.
我会从窗户溜走
I'll slip out the window,
你可以用打结的毛巾做梯子
and you can make a ladder from knotted towels
连在脸盆龙头上，好吗?
attached to the washbasin taps, okay?
朱恩
June.
Juney June.
嗯?Juney 朱恩
H? Juney June.
嗯?跟我说话
H? Talk to me.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
快点，我们现在就得逃跑，
Come on, we have to escape now,
不然我们就变成僵尸了
or else we'll end up resident zombies.
来吧,朱恩振作起来
Come on, June. Snap out of it.
-来吧，照我说的做…-让床!
-Come on, do as I... -Time for bed!
吉本斯
Gibbons.
我恨你
I hate you.
你是一个女巫!
You're a witch!
你婊子!你毁了我的生活!
You bitch! You're ruining my life!
我讨厌你!
I hate you!
珍妮弗!离开她!
Jennifer! Get off her!
停止它!
Stop it!
你他妈的婊子!
-You fucking bitch!
吉本斯
Gibbons.
你好,朱恩
Hello, June.
我是马乔里·华莱士
I'm Marjorie Wallace.
《星期日泰晤士报》的记者
A reporter for The Sunday Times.
我不知道你是否被允许阅读这篇文章
I don't know if you were allowed to read the article
我写了关于你的审判
I wrote about your trial.
我看过你写的东西
I've read your writing.
百事可乐上瘾者那天晚上让我熬夜到凌晨2点
Pepsi-Cola Addict  had me up the other night until- 00 a.m.
我爱不释手
I couldn't put it down.
你有非凡的想象力
You have an extraordinary imagination.
看到普雷斯顿被百事可乐淹没
The vision of Preston drowning in Pepsi-Cola.
你很擅长处理紧张感
You're very good with tension.
我想多读一些你的作品
I should like to read more of your writing.
如果你是…
If you were...
告诉你的故事……
telling your story...
通过我……
through me...
你希望你的人生怎么开始?
...how would you want yours to begin?
也许我应该开始……
Perhaps I would start...
她会没事的
She'll be all right.
时间到了
Time's up.
她在重症监护室做短期检查
She's on short visits in Intensive.
请告诉医生他必须回来
Please tell the doctor that must come back.
我们想在一起它是不正确的
We want to be together. It's not right.
不!
No!
!
你混蛋!
You bastards!
不!
No!
不!不!
No! No!
我们必须停下来
We have to stop.
必须有所不同
It has to be different.
我知道
I know.
没有更多的战斗
No more fighting.
我们得重新开始我们的生活
We need to get our lives together
在玛乔丽的书出版之前
before Marjorie's book comes out.
这将是辉煌的一天
It'll be a glorious day.
我们会以布罗德莫的女王的身份走出这里
We'll walk out of here as queens of Broadmoor.
我们会出名
We'll be famous.
如果门口有摄影师，我们应该挥手
If there are photographers at the gates, we should wave.
是的
Yeah.
-是的不是坏,是吗?
-Yeah. -Not bad, eh?
我们应该戒烟
We should stop smoking.
皇后不吸烟
Queens don't smoke.
我不知道你的名字
I don't know your name.
珍妮
-Jenny.
黛比?
Debbie?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
罗恩要把他的孩子给我
Ron is going to give me his baby.
谢谢你,耶稣
Thank you, Jesus.
这是行不通的
It's not gonna work.
你不能只用他的精子
You can't just use his sperm.
你只是嫉妒，因为我要当妈妈了
You're just jealous because I'm going to be a mother
和你不是
and you're not.
你也一样
It's the same game with you.
怎么，你要和罗恩私奔吗?
What, you gonna run off with Ron?
我死后还有家庭吗?
Have a family when I die?
他会是你的双胞胎兄弟
He'll be your twin.
别傻了
Don't be stupid.
你太漂亮了，不能先死
You're too pretty to die first.
那又怎样?
So what?
但如果我死了，你会忘记的
But if I die, you'll just get over it.
你是坚强的那个
You're the strong one.
战斗机-你真的这么想吗?
-Fighter. -Is that what you really think?
不,我不会
No, I won't.
我不想要悲伤
I don't want the grief.
-没用的是的,它会
-It's not gonna work. -Yes, it will.
我发现他因为过失杀人罪被关在这里
So, I found out he's in here for manslaughter.
是的，我知道，我知道
Yeah, I know, I know.
但他说他不是故意的
But he said he didn't mean it.
我确实做过被勒死的梦
I did have a dream about being strangled.
我只希望他不是赤手空拳
I just hope he didn't use his bare hands.
嘿，今天轮到你吃饭了
Hey, it's your turn to eat today.
好的请坐
All right. Take a seat, please.
继续
Go on.
哦,谢谢
Oh, thanks.
不!
No!
-不!
-No!
不，这不是她的错!
No, it's not her fault!
-不!
-No!
不!
No!
!
对不起,朱恩
I'm sorry, June.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起,朱恩
I'm sorry, June.
为什么要给女孩们注射镇定剂?
Why have the girls been sedated?
这是一个愤怒
It's an outrage.
他们迷路了，被彼此困住了
They're lost, trapped by each other.
他们没有危险
They're not dangerous.
医生-打扰一下，玛乔丽
DR.- Excuse me, Marjorie.
你在夺走他们的未来
You're taking away their future.
博士-收集一个杀人犯的精子装在瓶子里
DR.- Collecting a murderer's sperm in a bottle.
那是什么样的未来?
What kind of future is that?
她们是敏感的女孩
They are sensitive girls.
他们是作家你知道的
They are writers. You know that.
玛乔丽，他们就是控制不住自己
Marjorie, they just can't help themselves.
他们甚至都不想这么做
They don't even seem to want to.
当他们能证明他们是这样做的时候，我会很高兴地交出他们
When they can show that they do, I will happily hand them over.
但我们都无法控制这一点
But neither of us have any control over that.
而且我认为这不会很快发生
And I don't see it happening anytime soon.
我不会放过你的
I'm not letting this go.
让我毫无感觉
Leaves me no feeling in me.
我给你写了几首诗
I wrote you some poems.
我不能，我不能再写了
I can't, I can't write anymore.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我对理智和疯狂免疫
-I am iune from sanity or insanity
我是一个空空的礼物盒;
I am an empty present box;
全部打开，交给别人处理
all unwrapped for someone else's disposal.
我是一个被丢弃的蛋壳，
I am a thrown away egg-shell,
我体内没有生命，
With no life inside me,
因为我是不可触碰的
for I am not touchable,
不过是虚无的奴隶
but a slave to nothingness.
“鲍比，你说呢
"And how do you suppose Bobby
能帮助我们的孩子活下去吗?”她问道
is going to help our child live?" she asked.
帕伦伯格医生用奇怪而疏远的眼睛盯着她
Dr. Pallenberg gazed at her with strange remote eyes.
房间里笼罩着一种深沉的寂静
The room took on the presence of a heavy hush
-伴随着暗影的低语-
-accompanied by the shadowed whispers -
一个日益增长的秘密
of a growing secret.
他轻轻一笑，握住她的手
He smiled lightly, taking her hands in his.
渐渐地，他说服米歇尔接受了他的计划
Gradually, he persuades Michelle to accept his plan.
-他们把厨房改造了
-They converted their kitchen
变成了一个临时手术室
into a makeshift operating theatre
米歇尔是他的助手
and, with Michelle as his assistant,
约翰·帕伦伯格把鲍比的心脏拔了出来
John Pallenberg plucks Bobby's heart from his body
并植入婴儿韦恩体内
and implants it in baby Wayne.
这对父母保守秘密很好
The parents keep their secret well.
韦恩长成了一个了不起的孩子，
Wayne grows into a remarkable child,
就他的年龄来说已经很高级了
very advanced for his age.
但在七个月大的时候，
But at seven months,
韦恩震惊了米歇尔，他说……
Wayne shocks Michelle by saying...
“鲍比
"Bobby.
我希望鲍比”
I want Bobby."
他的父母不知道该说什么
His parents didn't know what to say
因为鲍比牺牲了自己的生命
because Bobby had sacrificed his life
为了救他
in order to save him.
你们俩都好吗?
How are you both doing?
我们感觉很好
We feel fine.
我们看起来还好吗?
Do we look fine?
你看起来很好
You look good.
我看起来很好
I look good.
你呢，珍妮?
How about you, Jenny?
你一直在吃东西吗?
Have you been eating?
我很好
I'm good.
我走了再吃
I'll eat when I'm gone.
马乔里……
Marjorie...
你在听吗?
Are you listening?
是的
Yes.
我有事要告诉你
Got something to tell you.
那是什么?
What's that?
我要死了
I'm going to die.
什么让你想到死亡?
What makes you think of death?
我只知道
I just know.
双胞胎们，好消息来了
Twinnies, the news is good.
勒·库特尔医生觉得你已经大有进步了
Dr. Le Couteur feels you've improved enough
让他签下转会到威尔士
for him to sign the transfer to Wales.
你是认真的吗?
Are you being for real?
是的
Yes.
我们离开这里吗?
We're leaving here?
我们离开我们离开的时候,六月
We're leaving. We're leaving, June.
我告诉你
I told you.
哦,我的上帝
Oh, my God.
这是美好的一天，这是美好的一天
It's a good day, it's a good day,
因为阳光明媚，鸟儿…
because the sun's shining and the birds...
-今天天气不错我告诉你-他们说只有几周时间
-It's a good day. I told you. -They saying it's only weeks.
我真为我们感到高兴
Oh, I'm so happy for us.
琼恩，这是11年的地狱
Oh, June, it's been 11 years of hell.
我们可以给你任何衣服
We can bring you whichever clothes
你会想穿出去的
you'd like to wear out of here.
也许一些牛仔裤吗?
Maybe some jeans?
也许裙子
Maybe skirts.
亲爱的,
Sweetheart,
你得照顾好自己
you need to take care of yourself
所以你出去的时候很健康
so you're healthy on the way out.
她会没事的，妈妈
She'll be fine, Muy.
我近30
I'm nearly 30.
如果我再胖一点会更漂亮吗?
Would I be prettier if I put on weight?
就几周
Just a couple of weeks.
不会太久的
It won't seem so long.
你的人生还长着呢
You've got your whole life ahead of you.
你,太
You, too.
运输走了
Transport leaving.
车离开
Van leaving.
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮,我们回家了
Jenny, we're home.
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮,醒来
Jenny, wake up.
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮-这是游戏吗?
-Jenny. -Is this a game?
不
No.
珍妮?
Jenny?
帮助我
Help me.
是什么……她怎么了?
What's... what's wrong with her?
头里
-Come on.
珍妮
-Jenny.
珍妮!
-Jenny!
珍妮
Jenny.
-Jenny.
珍妮!
Jenny!
呼吸,请
Breathe, please.
拜托
Please.
请醒来
Please wake up.
珍妮,醒来
Jenny, wake up.
这一点都不好笑了起床了
It's not funny anymore. Get up.
珍妮,醒醒吧!
Jenny, wake up!
醒来这一点都不好笑!
Wake up. It's not funny anymore!
求求你，求求你，起来
Please, please, get up.
珍妮,请
Jenny, please.
这一点都不好笑，一点都不好笑
It's not funny, it's not funny.
别玩游戏了，珍妮起床了
Stop playing games, Jenny. Get up.
站起来,珍妮!
Stand up, Jenny!
珍妮,起来
Jenny, get up.